David Locke Papers MS122
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Dagomba Dance Drumming materials, 1989 -- 2010; MS122.002; 788 Digital Object(s)
  - Tora, group dance, 1989 -- 2010; MS122.002.002; 58 Digital Object(s)
    - Tora Tora lead lunga drum language audio (2a) tom Tora to tom Tora, 2010; MS122.002.002.00046; Locke, David
    - Tora Tora lead lunga drum language audio (2b) tom Tora to tom Tora, 2010; MS122.002.002.00047; Locke, David
    - Tora Tora lead lunga drum language audio (3) tom Tora tom Tora tom Tora kul tom Tora, 2010; MS122.002.002.00048; Locke, David
    - Tora Tora lead lunga drum language audio (4a) to tom Tora to tom Tor' kul tom baa tom Tora, 2010; MS122.002.002.00049; Locke, David
    - Tora Tora lead lunga drum language audio (4b, 4c) to Tora to tom Tora tom baa tom Tora, 2010; MS122.002.002.00050; Locke, David
    - Tora Tora answer lunga drum language audio (1a) gbang bi yeli o, 2010; MS122.002.002.00051; Locke, David
    - Tora Tora answer lunga drum language audio (1b) gbang bi yeli o, 2010; MS122.002.002.00052; Locke, David
    - Tora Tora answer lunga drum language audio (1c) gbang bi yeli o, 2010; MS122.002.002.00053; Locke, David
    - Tora Tora lead gung-gong drum language audio (1a, 1b) to bi yeli o kul sagiri si ka nya, 2010; MS122.002.002.00054; Locke, David
    - Tora Tora lead gung-gong drum language audio (2) ka nya ka nya ka nya, 2010; MS122.002.002.00055; Locke, David
    - Tora Tora lead gung-gong drum language audio (3) ka nya ka nya ka to ka nya, 2010; MS122.002.002.00056; Locke, David
    - Tora Tora lead gung-gong drum language audio (4) ka nya ka nya ka to to ka nya, 2010; MS122.002.002.00057; Locke, David
    - Tora Tora lead gung-gong drum language audio (5) ka nya ka nya to ka nya, 2010; MS122.002.002.00058; Locke, David
  - Nakohi-waa, occupational lineage dance, 1993 -- 2010; MS122.002.003; 35 Digital Object(s)
    Nakohiwa is the butcher's dance. Butchers were incorporated into Dagomba society by Naa Dimani and have their own patrilineage similar to that of the drummers.
    - Story of Nakohi-waa, Dance Drumming for Butchers, 1993; MS122.002.003.00001; Locke, David; Lunna, Abubakari
      Told by Abubakari Lunna on May 21, 1993. Edited by David Locke. Story of the Nakohi-waa dance and drumming rhythm.
    - Nakohi-waa lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.003.00002; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.003.00003; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.003.00004; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.003.00005; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.003.00006; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa answer lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.003.00007; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa answer lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.003.00008; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa answer lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.003.00009; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa answer lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.003.00010; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa answer lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.003.00011; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.003.00012; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.003.00013; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.003.00014; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.003.00015; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.003.00016; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa answer gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.003.00017; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa answer gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.003.00018; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.003.00019; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.003.00020; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Nakohi-waa drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.003.00021; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Nakohi-waa answer gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.003.00022; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa answer gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.003.00023; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead lunga drum language audio (1) yeng ka n-fawa, 2010; MS122.002.003.00024; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead lunga drum language audio (2) magnun dang zhini o zuu n-diri naam, 2010; MS122.002.003.00025; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead lunga drum language audio (3) tabili gabili dini tabili gabli, 2010; MS122.002.003.00026; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead lunga drum language audio (4) yeng kani fawa, 2010; MS122.002.003.00027; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa answer lunga drum language audio (1), 2010; MS122.002.003.00028; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead gung-gong drum language audio (1) to to, 2010; MS122.002.003.00029; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead gung-gong drum language audio (2-1) naa gno o ti naa gno, 2010; MS122.002.003.00030; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead gung-gong drum language audio (2-2) o nim m-bala to ti naa gno, 2010; MS122.002.003.00031; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead gung-gong drum language audio (3) ka gnuni ka pa naa gno ka gnuni, 2010; MS122.002.003.00032; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead gung-gong drum language audio (4) to ti naa gno maa gno tum, 2010; MS122.002.003.00033; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa lead gung-gong drum language audio (5) nakohi naa o nim sagi di, 2010; MS122.002.003.00034; Locke, David
    - Nakohi-waa answer gung-gong drum language audio (1) naa gno to ti naa gno, 2010; MS122.002.003.00035; Locke, David
  - Dikala, occupational lineage dance, 2001 -- 2010; MS122.002.004; 26 Digital Object(s)
    Dikala is the music of the blacksmiths and is one of the older drum compositions of the Dagombas. The blacksmiths were incorporated into Dagomba society by Naa Luro. Naa Darizeau, who preceded Naa Luro, was killed by the Gonjas but was never buried and the proper funeral rights were never performed for him. Naa Luro wanted to confront the Gonjas for his body, but had to cross a river to reach their land. The blacksmiths had to be summoned to fashion tools for the woodworkers to make a bridge. The drum language for Dikala says "if you refuse a chief you will be killed," which is a reference to the fact that the blacksmith family was originally reluctant to be part of the royal court.
    - Story of Dikala, Dance Drumming for Blacksmiths, 2002; MS122.002.004.00001; Locke, David; Lunna, Abubakari
      Told by Abubakari Lunna, March 7, 2002. Edited by David Locke. Story of the origins of the Dikala dance and drumming rhythm.
    - Dikala lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.004.00002; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dikala lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.004.00003; Locke, David
    - Dikala lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.004.00004; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dikala lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.004.00005; Locke, David
    - Dikala lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.004.00006; Locke, David
    - Dikala answer lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.004.00007; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dikala answer lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.004.00008; Locke, David
    - Dikala answer lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.004.00009; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dikala answer lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.004.00010; Locke, David
    - Dikala answer lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.004.00011; Locke, David
    - Dikala lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.004.00012; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dikala lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.004.00013; Locke, David
    - Dikala lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.004.00014; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dikala lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.004.00015; Locke, David
    - Dikala lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.004.00016; Locke, David
    - Dikala ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.004.00017; Locke, David
    - Dikala drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.004.00018; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Dikala drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.004.00019; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Dikala lead lunga drumming transcription, 2010; MS122.002.004.00020; Locke, David
    - Dikala lead lunga drum language audio (1) gnun sagirisi naa noli gnuni nin kani, 2010; MS122.002.004.00021; Locke, David
    - Dikala lead lunga drum language audio (2) gnuni sagirisi naa noli gnuni nin kani, 2010; MS122.002.004.00022; Locke, David
    - Dikala answer lunga drum language audio (1) gnuni sagirisi ku ba ku, 2010; MS122.002.004.00023; Locke, David
    - Dikala answer lunga drum language audio (2) to ku ba ku, 2010; MS122.002.004.00024; Locke, David
    - Dikala lead gung-gong drum language audio (1) gnuni sagirisi ku ba ku, 2010; MS122.002.004.00025; Locke, David
    - Dikala lead gung-gong drum language audio (2) to ku ba ku, 2010; MS122.002.004.00026; Locke, David
  - Naa Zangina, 2001; MS122.002.005; 1 Digital Object(s)
    Zangina was a son of Naa Tutuari. When Naa Tutuari passed away, he was succeeded by Naa Zaali, who was in turn succeeded by Naa Gungobli. After Naa Gungobli passed away, many of Naa Tutuaris sons contested for the skin. The elders had trouble deciding who to make the next Yaa-naa, so they went to ask the chief of the Mamprussis to help with the decision, as the Dagombas had once done for them. The chief chose Zangina, much to the dismay of his older brothers. Note: Unlike other history stories there is no dance-drumming piece associated with the story of Naa Zangina. However, because of his significance in the history of Dagbon, David Locke asked Alhaji to narrate the story of this important chief. There is no dance drumming for this item of repertoire.
    - Story of Naa Zangina, 2001; MS122.002.005.00001; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
      Told by Abubakari Lunna on February 5, 2001. Edited by David Locke. Story of how Naa Zangina became chief.
  - Suligu, solo dance, 2001 -- 2010; MS122.002.006; 24 Digital Object(s)
    Suligu is the appellation for Diari-lana Bukali. This story starts during the time of the last war between the Dagombas and the Gonjas. The Gonja chief, Kumpatia, was advancing on Yendi, and Naa Zanjina couldn't get any support from the other chiefs or his brothers, so he sent Diari-lana to convince Naa Siali and his men to fight. The word suligu means hawk, and the appellation is a tribute to Bukali's formidable strength as a warrior.
    - Story of Suligu, appellation of Diari-lan' Bukali, 2002; MS122.002.006.00001; Locke, David; Lunna, Abubakari
      Told by Abubakari Lunna on March 29, 2002. Edited by David Locke. Story of the origins of the Suliga drumming rhythm, which celebrates the character of the chief Diari-lan' Bukali.
    - Suligu lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.006.00002; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Suligu lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.006.00003; Locke, David
    - Suligu lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.006.00004; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Suligu lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.006.00005; Locke, David
    - Suligu lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.006.00006; Locke, David
    - Suligu answer lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.006.00007; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Suligu answer lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.006.00008; Locke, David
    - Suligu answer lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.006.00009; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Suligu answer lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.006.00010; Locke, David
    - Suligu answer lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.006.00011; Locke, David
    - Suligu lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.006.00012; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Suligu lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.006.00013; Locke, David
    - Suligu lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.006.00014; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Suligu lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.006.00015; Locke, David
    - Suligu lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.006.00016; Locke, David
    - Suligu ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.006.00017; Locke, David
    - Suligu drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.006.00018; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Suligu drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.006.00019; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Suligu lead lunga drum language audio (1) To zam bugli dapala, 2010; MS122.002.006.00020; Locke, David
    - Suligu lead lunga drum language audio (2) ma mini mini gnuni kpuri, 2010; MS122.002.006.00021; Locke, David
    - Suligu lead lunga drum language audio (3) baa ku nyomsi nogna, 2010; MS122.002.006.00022; Locke, David
    - Suligu lead lunga drum language audio (4) bi yeri ma jogujogu, 2010; MS122.002.006.00023; Locke, David
    - Suligu answer lunga drum language audio (1) ma mini o n-kpoi hoi bugli no ku o kpoi zami kpemba la, 2010; MS122.002.006.00024; Locke, David
  - Dogu, solo dance, 2001 -- 2010; MS122.002.007; 54 Digital Object(s)
    Dogu is the appellation of Tugu-lana Yemusa. Yemusa is the son of Naa Andani Sigli, and he was born on the same day that Andani killed Kumpatia, king of the Gonjas. Yemusa was made the regent when his father died. In a town called Bagli, there was another person named Yemusa who was also made the regent at his father's funeral. His drummers told him to use one of Tugu-lana Yemusa's appellations for himself. When Tugu-lana Yemusa found out that another Yemusa was using his appellation, he became jealous and went to Bagli to challenge him. Tugu-lana injured the other Yemusa in an effort to make him stop using the appellations, but he refused, and eventually Tugu-lana killed him. The drum language for Doggu means "he killed him because of a name." Today, Dogu is used as an appellation for all regents.
    - Story of Dogu, appellation of Tugu-lan Yemusa, 2001; MS122.002.007.00001; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
      Told by Abubakari Lunna on February 1, 2001. Edited by David Locke. Describes the history of the Dogu rhythm, which tells the story of how Tugu-lan Yemusa became chief.
    - Dogu Mangli lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.007.00002; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
      African drumming; Ghanian music; Talking drums; Dagomba drumming
    - Dogu Mangli lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.007.00003; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.007.00004; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.007.00005; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.007.00006; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli answer lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.007.00007; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli answer lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.007.00008; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli answer lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.007.00009; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli answer lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.007.00010; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli answer lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.007.00011; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.007.00012; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.007.00013; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.007.00014; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.007.00015; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.007.00016; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.007.00017; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.007.00018; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Dogu Mangli drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.007.00019; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Dogu Tuli lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.007.00020; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.007.00021; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.007.00022; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.007.00023; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.007.00024; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli answer lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.007.00025; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli answer lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.007.00026; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli answer lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.007.00027; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli answer lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.007.00028; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli answer lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.007.00029; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.007.00030; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.007.00031; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.007.00032; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.007.00033; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.007.00034; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.007.00035; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.007.00036; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Dogu Tuli drumming ensemble audio, 2005; MS122.002.007.00037; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Dogu Mangli lead lunga drum language audio (1) nguni bormi ngo tilgi, 2010; MS122.002.007.00038; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli lead lunga drum language audio (1) m-bori mi no tiligi no cheli zuu yuli la, 2010; MS122.002.007.00039; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli lead lunga drum language audio (2) cheli zuu yuli la, 2010; MS122.002.007.00040; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli lead lunga drum language audio (3) ku n-zam bugli dapala, 2010; MS122.002.007.00041; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli lead lunga drum language audio (4a) ku n-zam bugli dapala zhiri kopelim ku sugiri noli, 2010; MS122.002.007.00042; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli lead lunga drum language audio (4b) ku n-zam bugli dapala zhiri kopelim ku sugiri noli, 2010; MS122.002.007.00043; Locke, David
    - Dogu Mangli answer lunga drum language audio (1) cheli yuli tagi yuli, 2010; MS122.002.007.00044; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli lead lunga drum language audio (1a) oku o oku o, 2010; MS122.002.007.00045; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli lead lunga drum language audio (1b) o-kpiya o-kpiya, 2010; MS122.002.007.00046; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli lead lunga drum language audio (2) zuu yuli oko o, 2010; MS122.002.007.00047; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli lead lunga drum language audio (3) bazhini cheli o yuli, 2010; MS122.002.007.00048; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli lead lunga drum language audio (4) to ku o to ku o, 2010; MS122.002.007.00049; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli lead lunga drum language audio (5) to ku o ku o ku o, 2010; MS122.002.007.00050; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli lead lunga drum language audio (6) ku o ku o ku o, 2010; MS122.002.007.00051; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli answer lunga drum language audio (1) to chel' yul' tag' yul' to, 2010; MS122.002.007.00052; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli answer lunga drum language audio (2) to chel' yul' tagi yul', 2010; MS122.002.007.00053; Locke, David
    - Dogu Tuli answer lunga drum language audio (3) yul' tag' yul', 2010; MS122.002.007.00054; Locke, David
  - Nantoo Nimdi, solo dance, 2001 -- 2010; MS122.002.008; 26 Digital Object(s)
    Nantoo Nimdo, which means poisoned meat, is the appellation for Naa Yakubu. The story tells of how Naa Yakubu became Yaa-naa because of the efforts of his zealous and powerful nephew, Idantoma. Because he had Idantoma as an ally, it would have been dangerous for someone to threaten Naa Yakubu, which is why he likens himself to poisoned meat. The drum language for Nantoo Nimdi says "I am poison for princes," which a warning to those who don't have the proper protections to stay away from Naa Yakubu.
    - Story of Nantoo Nimdi, appellation of Naa Yakuba, 2001; MS122.002.008.00001; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
      Told by Abubakari Lunna on March 2 and 6, 2001. Edited by David Locke. Describes the origins of the Nanto Nimdi rhythm that is played in honor of the chief Naa Yakuba.
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.008.00002; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.008.00003; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.008.00004; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.008.00005; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.008.00006; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi answer lunga vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.008.00007; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi answer lunga vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.008.00008; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi answer lunga drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.008.00009; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi answer lunga drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.008.00010; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi answer lunga drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.008.00011; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead gung-gong vocables audio, 2001; MS122.002.008.00012; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead gung-gong vocables notation, 2010; MS122.002.008.00013; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead gung-gong drumming audio, 2001; MS122.002.008.00014; Lunna, Abubakari; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead gung-gong drumming notation, 2010; MS122.002.008.00015; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead gung-gong drum language text, 2010; MS122.002.008.00016; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi ensemble rhythm notation, 2010; MS122.002.008.00017; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi drumming ensemble audio, live, 2008; MS122.002.008.00018; Agbekor Drum and Dance Society, Dagomba Section; Goldmann, Jonathan
    - Nantoo Nimdi drumming ensemble audio, multitrack aggregate, 2005; MS122.002.008.00019; Lunna, Abubakari; Wasserman, Luke
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead lunga drum language audio (1) Doo bi nye o to dapal', 2010; MS122.002.008.00020; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead lunga drum language audio (2) akul' dapal' Nantoo Nimdi, 2010; MS122.002.008.00021; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead lunga drum language audio (3) to Nimdi Nantoo Nimdi, 2010; MS122.002.008.00022; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead lunga drum language audio (4a) zangmi ka nya, 2010; MS122.002.008.00023; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi lead lunga drum language audio (4b) to zangmi ka nya, 2010; MS122.002.008.00024; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi answer lunga drum language audio (1) kagi sulisi, 2010; MS122.002.008.00025; Locke, David
    - Nantoo Nimdi answer lunga drum language audio (2) kagi sulisi, 2010; MS122.002.008.00026; Locke, David
  - Nagbiegu, solo dance, 2001 -- 2010; MS122.002.009; 35 Digital Object(s)